Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection MSS.040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2003 - Series II: Graphic Material, 40380
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40381
    - Williams, Richard: Bloo (commercial art), undated; 40390 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 153)
    - Williams, Richard: A CHRISTMAS CAROL, undated; 40389 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 154)
    - Williams, Richard: Cresta (commercial art), undated; 40388 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 155)
    - Williams, Richard: Johnson and Johnson (commercial art), undated; 40387 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 156)
    - Williams, Richard: THE PINK PANTHER, undated; 40386 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 157)
    - Williams, Richard: Tic-Tac (commercial art), undated; 40385 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 159)
    - Williams, Richard: TRANS-SIBERIAN EXPRESS, undated; 40384 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 160)
    - Williams, Richard: WHO FRAMED ROGER RABBIT, undated; 40383 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 161)
    - Williams, Richard: Various, undated; 40382 (Box 2003.II.A.4, Folder 162)
- Accretions 2003 - Series VI: Major Projects, 40288
  Series VI consists of research materials for major projects by Canemaker. Research notes, interview transcripts, correspondence and other related items used for specific projects by Canemaker are processed together to aid archival retrieval.
  - Subseries A: "The Art and Flair of Mary Blair", 40330
    Access to Series VI Subseries A of the 2003 Accretion has been restricted by the collection donor. These files will become avaiable to researchers in March 2023.
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (draft manuscript), 2002; 40379 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 165)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (draft manuscript), 2002; 40378 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 166)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (edits and annotations), 2003; 40377 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 167)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (research notes), undated; 40376 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 168)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Barrier, Michael, undated; 40375 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 169)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Beckerman, Howard, undated; 40374 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 170)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Donovan, undated; 40373 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 171)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Kevin, undated; 40372 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 172)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee - biographical material, undated; 40371 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 173)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee: Correspondence: Fred Cline, undated; 40370 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 174)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee: Correspondence: Walt Disney, undated; 40369 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 175)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee: Correspondence (misc), undated; 40368 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 176)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Biographical material, undated; 40367 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 177)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Lee Blair, undated; 40366 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 178)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Walt Disney, undated; 40365 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 179)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: family, undated; 40364 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 180)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Dick Irvine, undated; 40363 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 181)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Jacqueline Kennedy, undated; 40362 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 182)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Jack Lavin, undated; 40361 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 183)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: House, undated; 40360 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 184)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Interviews, undated; 40359 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 185)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: News clippings, undated; 40358 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 186)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Photographs (digital copies), undated; 40357 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 187)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: South African Trip (Disney), undated; 40356 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 188)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Chamberlain, Jeanne, undated; 40355 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 189)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Cline, Fred, undated; 40354 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 190)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Cole Black and the Seven Drarves (musical with art by M.B.), 1946; 40353 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 191)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Cole Black and the Seven Drarves (cassette tape), 1946; 40352 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 192)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Crump, Roland, undated; 40351 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 193)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Davis, Marc, undated; 40350 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 194)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Disney, Roy, undated; 40349 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 195)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Docter, Pete, undated; 40348 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 196)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Fujikawa, Gyo, undated; 40347 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 197)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Garner, Lou, undated; 40346 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 198)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Giaimo, Michael, undated; 40345 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 199)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Graver, Neil, undated; 40344 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 200)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Hench, John, undated; 40343 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 201)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Hench, John, undated; 40342 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder Johnson, Michael)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Lefton, Wendy, undated; 40341 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 203)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Marling, Karal Ann, undated; 40340 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 204)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS O'Connor, Ken, undated; 40339 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 205)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Perine, Robert, undated; 40338 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 206)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Rich, Maggie, undated; 40337 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 207)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Shue, Ken, undated; 40336 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 208)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Sklar, Martin, undated; 40335 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 209)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Smith, Lella, undated; 40334 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 210)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Thomas, Frank, undated; 40333 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 211)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Tieman, Robert, undated; 40332 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 212)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS World's Fair: It's a Small World, 1964; 40331 (Box 2003.VI.A.B.4, Folder 213)
  - Subseries B: Vladimir (William) Tytla, "Animation's Michelangelo", 40304
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1975-1988; 40329 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 214)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1992; 40328 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 215)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1993; 40327 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 216)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1994-1996; 40326 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 217)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, 1997-2002; 40325 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 218)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Canemaker, undated; 40324 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 219)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Correspondence: Various, undated; 40323 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 220)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Disney Giant (biography of Tytla), undated; 40322 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 221)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Interview (cassette tape), 1992; 40321 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 222)
    - Tytla, Adrienne: Photos, undated; 40320 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 223)
    - Tytla, Peter, undated; 40319 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 224)
    - Tytla, Peter: Animation Journal, 1994; 40318 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 225)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Animation's Michelangelo, 1975; 40317 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 226)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Biographical information, untited; 40316 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 227)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Cinefastique (v.5 no.3), 1976; 40315 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 228)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Art Babbitt, 1933-1965; 40314 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 229)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: John Cannemaker, 1975-1995; 40313 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 230)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Walt Disney, 1994-1956; 40312 (Box 2003.VI.A.5, Folder 231)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Family, 1929-1939; 40311 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 232)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Correspondence: Various, 1929-1968; 40310 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 233)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Disney production documents, undated; 40309 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 234)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Interviews, undated; 40308 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 235)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: News articles, 1940-1995; 40307 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 236)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Promotional Folder: Katonah Museum of Art, 1994; 40306 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 237)
    - Tytla, Vladimir: Research notes (Canemaker), undated; 40305 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 238)
  - Subseries C: "Walt Disney's Nine Old Men and the Art of Animation", 40289
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to book, 1998; 40303 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 239)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to book, 1999-2001; 40302 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 240)
    - Canemaker, John: Research materials, undated; 40301 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 241)
    - Clark, Les, undated; 40300 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 242-244)
    - Davis, Marc, undated; 40299 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 245-248)
    - FRANK AND OLLIE, undated; 40298 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 249)
    - Johnston, Ollie, undated; 40297 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 250-252)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated; 40296 (Box 2003.VI.B.C.6, Folder 253-254)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated; 40295 (Box 2003.VI.C.7, Folder 255-257)
    - Kimball, Ward, undated; 40294 (Box 2003.VI.C.7, Folder 258-260)
    - Larson, Eric, undated; 40293 (Box 2003.VI.C.7, Folder 261-263)
    - Lounsbery, John, undated; 40292 (Box 2003.VI.C.7, Folder 264)
    - Reitherman, Wolfgang, undated; 40291 (Box 2003.VI.C.7, Folder 265-266)
    - Thomas, Frank, undated; 40290 (Box 2003.VI.C.7, Folder 267-272)
- Accretions 2003 - Oversize - Series II: Graphic Material, 40262
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40263
    - Babbitt, Art, undated; 40287 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 91)
    - Blair, Mary: "Art and Flair of Mary Blair" (galley proofs), undated; 40286 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 94)
    - Blair, Mary: Assorted, undated; 40285 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 96-97)
    - Blair, Mary: Christmas card designs, undated; 40284 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 98)
    - Blair, Mary: Commercial art, undated; 40283 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 101)
    - Blair, Mary: It's a Small World, undated; 40282 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 102)
    - Clark, Les, undated; 40281 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 109-110)
    - Davis, Marc, undated; 40280 (Box 2003.II.A.8, Folder 111-112)
    - Ferguson, Norman, undated; 40279 (Box 2003.II.A.9, Folder 113)
    - Iwerks, Ub, undated; 40278 (Box 2003.II.A.9, Folder 116)
    - Johnston, Ollie, undated; 40277 (Box 2003.II.A.9, Folder 117)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated; 40276 (Box 2003.II.A.9, Folder 120-122)
    - Kimball, Ward, undated; 40275 (Box 2003.II.A.10, Folder 125-126)
    - Larson, Eric, undated; 40274 (Box 2003.II.A.10, Folder 127)
    - Lounsbery, John, undated; 40273 (Box 2003.II.A.10, Folder 129)
    - Luske, Ham, undated; 40272 (Box 2003.II.A.10, Folder 130)
    - Moore, Fred, undated; 40271 (Box 2003.II.A.10, Folder 132)
    - Reitherman, Wolfgang, undated; 40270 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 133)
    - Thomas, Frank, undated; 40269 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 134)
    - Tytla, William, undated; 40268 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 143)
    - Tytla, William, undated; 40267 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 145)
    - Williams, Richard, undated; 40266 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 158)
    - Williams, Richard, undated; 40265 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 163)
    - Unknown artist, undated; 40264 (Box 2003.II.A.11, Folder 164)
- Accretions 2008 - Series I: Documentary Material, 40139
  - Subseries A: Subjects, 40198
    - Animation Articles, 1981 - 2005; 40261 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 1)
    - Awards: 33rd Annie Awards (LA), 2006; 40260 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 2)
    - Exhibitions: Animated Art from Walt Disney Studios: The Lucius T. and Jane Scott B. Chapin Collection (Marsh Art Gallery, VA), 2000; 40259 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 3)
    - Exhibitions: The Art of Fantasia (Cartoon Art Museum, CA), 1990 - 1991; 40258 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitions: Independent Voices: The Art of Animation (Grand Valley State University, MI), 2001; 40257 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions: Oscar Howe: A Retrospective Exhibition (Thomas Gilcrease Museum Association, OK), 1982; 40256 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 6)
    - Exhibitions: Peanuts (Cartoon Research Library, OH), 2000 - 2001; 40255 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 7)
    - Exhibitions: Pixar: 20 Years of Animation (Museum of Modern Art, NY), 2005 - 2006; 40254 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 8)
    - Exhibitions: Polish Animated Film (Museum of Modern Art, NY), 2003; 40253 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 9)
    - Exhibitions: Tanja Softic': Recent Works on Paper (Marsh Art Gallery, VA), 1981 - 2005; 40252 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 10)
    - Exhibitions: Vilallonga: Poetic Symbolism from Barcelona (City of Thousand Oaks, CA), 2000; 40251 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 11)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Anima Mundi (Brazil) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2006; 40250 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 12)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Animadrid (Spain), 2005; 40249 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 13)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Animadrid (Spain), 2006; 40248 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 14)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Annecy (France), 2005; 40247 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 15)
    - Festivals & Screenings: The Cartoon Medicine Show: Animated Cartoons from the Collection of the National Library of Medicine (National Library of Medicine, DC), 2006; 40246 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 16)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 41st Chicago International Film Festival (IL), 2005; 40245 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 17)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Fantoche (Switzerland), 2005; 40244 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 18)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Festival du Court Metrage de Clermont-Ferrand (France), 2006; 40243 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 19)
    - Festivals & Screenings: I Castelli Animati (Italy) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2005; 40242 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 20)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 21st International Short Film Festival Berlin (Germany), 2005; 40241 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 21)
    - Festivals & Screenings: JazzToons with John Canemaker (Jacob Burns Film Center, NY), 2004; 40240 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 22)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Les Sommets du Cinema D'Animation (Canada), 2005; 40239 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 23)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Margaret Mead Film & Video Festival (NY), 2005; 40238 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 24)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Ottawa Student Animation Festival (Canada), 2003; 40237 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 25)
    - Festivals & Screenings: Ottawa International Animation Festival (Canada), 2005; 40236 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 26)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 13th Stuttgart International Festival of Animated Film (Germany), 2006; 40235 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 27)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 32nd Telluride Film Festival (CO) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2005; 40234 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 28)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 33rd Telluride Film Festival (CO) ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2006; 40233 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 29)
    - Festivals & Screenings: VisionFest (Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis, IN), 2005; 40232 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 30)
    - Festivals & Screenings: 17th World Festival of Animated Film (Croatia), 2006; 40231 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 31)
    - "Avoid Eye Contact" NYC Independent Animation Panel, 2004; 40230 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 32)
    - Associazione Fabrizio Bellocchio Onlus, n.d.; 40229 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 33)
    - Cartoon Research Library, Ohio State University, 2006; 40228 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 34)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: 1998 Fall & Holiday Preview, 40227 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 35)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: Summer Preview 2001, 40226 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 36)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: 2005 Preview (Electronic press kit), 40225 (Box 2008.I.A.1, Folder 37)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: ANTZ, 1998; 40224 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 38)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: CHICKEN RUN, 2000; 40223 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 39)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: MADAGASCAR (Electronic press kit), 2005; 40222 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 40)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: OVER THE HEDGE (Electronic press kit), 2006; 40221 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 41)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: PRINCE OF EGYPT, 1998; 40220 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 42)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: THE ROAD TO EL DORADO, 2000; 40219 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 43)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SHARK TALE (Electronic press kit), 2004; 40218 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 44)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SHREK, n.d.; 40217 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 45)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SINBAD: LEGEND OF THE SEVEN SEAS, 2003; 40216 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 46)
    - DreamWorks Pictures: SPIRIT: STALLION OF THE CIMARRON, 2002; 40215 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 47)
    - Go Fish Pictures: GHOST IN THE SHELL 2: INNOCENCE, 2004; 40214 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 48)
    - Go Fish Pictures: MILLENNIUM ACTRESS, 2003; 40213 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 49)
    - iotaCenter, n.d.; 40212 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 50)
    - The OpenEnded Group, 40211 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 51)
    - Pacific Film Archive, University of California ***see*** Series II-B for oversize material, 2006; 40210 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder data_value_missing_719f33721bcd8af864b23181f34c7945)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: Exhibition ***see*** Exhibitions: Pixar: 20 Years of Animation, Museum of Modern Art, NY (Accretions 2008 - Series I: Documentary Material, Subseries A: Subjects), 2005 - 2006; 40209
    - Pixar Animation Studios: CARS (Electronic press kit), 2006; 40208 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 53)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: FINDING NEMO, 2003; 40207 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 54)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: THE INCREDIBLES, 2004; 40206 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 55)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: THE INCREDIBLES (Electronic press kit), 2004; 40205 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 56)
    - Pixar Animation Studios: TOY STORY 2, 1999; 40204 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 57)
    - Soup2Nuts, n.d.; 40203 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 58)
    - Studio Ghibli: HOWL'S MOVING CASTLE, 2005; 40202 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 59)
    - Studio Ghibli: MIYAZAKI'S SPIRITED AWAY, 2002; 40201 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 60)
    - Twentieth Century Fox: ANASTASIA, 1997; 40200 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 61)
    - Vanguard Animation Studios: VALIANT, 2005; 40199 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 62)
  - Subseries B: People, 40140
    - Babbitt, Art, n.d.; 40197 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 63)
    - Bellocchio, Fabrizio ***see*** Associazione Fabrizio Bellocchio Onlus (Accretions 2008 - Series I: Documentary Material, Subseries A: Subjects), n.d.; 40196
    - Canemaker, John: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2002 - 2004; 40195 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 64)
    - Canemaker, John: Miscellaneous Publicity, n.d.; 40194 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 65)
    - Canemaker, John: Winsor McCay: His Life and Art (Revised & Expanded Edition), 2005; 40193 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 66)
    - Chomet, Sylvain: THE TRIPLETS OF BELLEVILLE, n.d.; 40192 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 67)
    - Davis, Marc, 2000; 40191 (Box 2008.I.A.B.2, Folder 68)
    - Disney, Walt: Annual Report, 1998; 40190 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 69)
    - Disney, Walt: Annual Report, 1999; 40189 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 70)
    - Disney, Walt: Canemaker article on closing of Disney's last hand-drawn animation studio, 2005; 40188 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 71)
    - Disney, Walt: Inter-office memo written by Walt Disney, 1935; 40187 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 72)
    - Disney, Walt: ATLANTIS: THE LOST EMPIRE, 2001; 40186 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 73)
    - Disney, Walt: BROTHER BEAR, 2003; 40185 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 74)
    - Disney, Walt: CHICKEN LITTLE (Electronic press kit), 2005; 40184 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 75)
    - Disney, Walt: THE CHRONICLES OF NARNIA: THE LION, THE WITCH AND THE WARDROBE (Electronic press kit), 2005; 40183 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 76)
    - Disney, Walt: THE EMPEROR'S NEW GROOVE, 2000 - 2001; 40182 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 77)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA 2000, 1999 - 2000; 40181 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 78)
    - Disney, Walt: HERCULES, 1997; 40180 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 79)
    - Disney, Walt: HOME ON THE RANGE, 2004; 40179 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 80)
    - Disney, Walt: HOME ON THE RANGE (Electronic press kit), n.d.; 40178 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 81)
    - Disney, Walt: THE HUNCHBACK OF NOTRE DAME, 1996; 40177 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 82)
    - Disney, Walt: LILO & STITCH, 2002; 40176 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 83)
    - Disney, Walt: MULAN, n.d.; 40175 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 84)
    - Disney, Walt: PIRATES OF THE CARIBBEAN: DEAD MAN'S CHEST (Electronic press kit), 2006; 40174 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 85)
    - Disney, Walt: POCAHONTAS, 1995; 40173 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 86)
    - Disney, Walt: POOH'S HEFFALUMP MOVIE, 2005; 40172 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 87)
    - Disney, Walt: TARZAN, 1999; 40171 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 88)
    - Disney, Walt: TEACHER'S PET, 2003; 40170 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 89)
    - Disney, Walt: TIM BURTON'S THE NIGHTMARE BEFORE CHRISTMAS: Presented for the First Time Ever in Disney Digital 3-D (Electronic press kit), 2006; 40169 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 90)
    - Disney, Walt: TREASURE PLANET, 2002; 40168 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 91)
    - Disney, Walt: THE WILD (Electronic pree kit), 2006; 40167 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 92)
    - Disney, Walt: Luca Raffaelli's Le Anime Disegnate: Il pensiero nei cartoon da Disney ai giapponesi e oltre, 2005; 40166 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 93)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d.; 40165 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 94)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d.; 40164 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 95)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d.; 40163 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 96)
    - Glad, Michael I.: Animation Art Collection, n.d.; 40162 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 97)
    - Halas, John & Batchelor, Joy, n.d.; 40161 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 98)
    - Hubley, John & Faith: Interview of Faith Hubley, 1996; 40160 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 99)
    - Hubley, John & Faith: FINIAN'S RAINBOW, 2001; 40159 (Box 2008.I.B.3, Folder 100)
    - Hurd, Earl, 2004; 40158 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 101)
    - Hykade, Andreas, 40157 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 102)
    - Johnston, Ollie: Correspondence with Canemaker, 1979 - 1991; 40156 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 103)
    - Kley, Heinrich, 1937 - 1939; 40155 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 104)
    - Kley, Heinrich, 2004; 40154 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 105)
    - Majolie, Bianca @ Blanche Hielborn, n.d.; 40153 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 106)
    - Majolie, Bianca @ Blanche Hielborn, n.d.; 40152 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 107)
    - McCay, Winsor: Canemaker correspondence with Maud H. Brown, 40151 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 108)
    - McCay, Winsor: Canemaker correspondence with Robert W. McCay, 40150 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 109)
    - McCay, Winsor: Canemaker correspondence with Ray Moniz, 40149 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 110)
    - McCay, Winsor: Various correspondences re: McCay, 40148 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 111)
    - McCay, Winsor: Various correspondences re: McCay, 40147 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 112)
    - McCay, Winsor: Interview of William R. Hearst, Jr., 1988; 40146 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 113)
    - McCay, Winsor: Interview of Irving Mendelsohn, 1974; 40145 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 114)
    - Reiniger, Lotte, 1982; 40144 (Box 2008.I.B.VI.A.B.C.4, Folder 115)
    - Thomas, Frank: Correspondence with Canemaker ***see*** Johnston, Ollie, 1976 - 2003; 40143